<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://BraveAlice.github.io</id>
    <title>BraveAlice</title>
    <updated>2021-11-20T21:10:40.854Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://BraveAlice.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://BraveAlice.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>Rescue PhD</subtitle>
    <logo>https://BraveAlice.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://BraveAlice.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2021, BraveAlice</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Am I in an abusive relationship?]]></title>
        <id>https://BraveAlice.github.io/post/am-i-in-an-abusive-relationship/</id>
        <link href="https://BraveAlice.github.io/post/am-i-in-an-abusive-relationship/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-19T12:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Everyone has arguments, and every supervisee disagrees with their supervisors from time to time.<br>
If this begins to form a consistent pattern, then it is an indication of domestic violence and abuse.</p>
<p>The answers to the following questions may help you:</p>
<p>Has your supervisor tried to keep you from seeing other supervisors, researchers or students?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor prevented you or made it hard for you to continue or start researching, or froming going to conference, or froming teaching modules?</p>
<p>Does your supervisor unjustly accuse you of stupid, bad at language or your research knowledge?</p>
<p>Does your supervisor constantly belittle or humililate you, or regularly criticise or insult you?</p>
<p>Are you ever afraid of your supervisor?</p>
<p>Have you ever changed your behaviour  because you are afraid of what your supervisor might do or say to you?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever change any part of your or research project deliberately?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever hurt or threatened you or your academic results (spiritual child)?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever kept you short of money so you are unable to continue research and other necessary support for yourself and your research?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever forced you to do something that you really did not want to do?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever tried to prevent you from taking necessary medication, or seeking medical help when you felt you needed it?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever tried to control you by telling you that you could be withdrawed because you need his/her approval to proceed your research?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever threatened to stop your research project, or said he would refuse to let you continue, or even to cancell them, if you dont listen to him/her?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever forced or harassed you to have sex with him/her or with other people? Has he/she made you participate in sexual activities that you were uncomfortable with?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor made sexual or race comments that you were uncomfortable with?</p>
<p>Has your supervisor ever tried to prevent your leaving the office or meeting room?</p>
<p>Does your supervisor blame you for his late or no feedback and guidance on your work?</p>
<p>These questions are inspired by<br>
https://www.womensaid.org.uk/the-survivors-handbook/am-i-in-an-abusive-relationship/</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>